star-ecentral.com 2008-06-16

# The Star Online: Privacy Statement

### Privacy Statement for The Star Online

Star Publications (Malaysia) Berhad (co. no. 10894-D) has created this privacy statement to demonstrate its firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website, The Star Online. 

Our Web servers do not automatically recognise specific information about individual users on our site. In addition, our servers do not automatically record information regarding a user's e-mail address unless the user supplies it. 

We collect information about users during the registration process for certain parts of our site; through their participation in certain activities, including contests, forums, and polls; and through the use of cookies. When you request pages from our server, it automatically collects some information about your preferences, including your IP address. We use this to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our site. 

We use cookies so that you do not have to enter your login information each time you visit our site. 

The information collected is meant to identify the broad demographic profile of our users. This information does not contain anything that can identify users individually. We may combine demographic information supplied by a subscriber at registration with site usage data to provide profiles, in aggregate form, about our users and their preferences in the content of the site and advertising. You may receive periodic mailings from us with information on new products or services in our newspaper or on our site. 

The user-supplied information collected through the registration process, surveys, contest entry forms, polls or other similar vehicles is used to improve the content of our site, or used for Star Publications (Malaysia) Berhad's marketing purposes. It is not shared with other organisations for commercial purposes unless specifically stated. We may use such information for targeting appropriate editorial or advertising content to users but users will always be able to opt out of such mailings. 

This site makes information sharing, feedback, forums, and/or message boards available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. We request that users treat each other with courtesy and mutual respect. 

This site contains links to other sites. The Star Online is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such sites. The Star Online has also established relationships with partners but such relationships are generally technical in nature, or content collaborations. If any partner has access to any information entered by users in our database, this fact shall be disclosed to the user upon initiating the registration process. Users who feel they do not wish their information to be shared by anyone other than The Star Online may then opt out of completing the registration. 

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. When a user is asked to provide his/her credit card information, we provide a secure environment through our partners' systems (using industry standard SSL or SET protocols) for this purpose. 

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, you may contact: 

I.Star Division  
Star Publications (Malaysia) Berhad  
Level 7 Menara Star  
15 Jln 16/11  
46350 Petaling Jaya  
MALAYSIA
